A Finding Aid to the Howard Wise Gallery Records, 1943-1989, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1950-1984; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 3.4 Linear feet Boxes 3-6
  - Getman, William, 1957-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Gilleran, Peter J., 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Gillet, Roger Edgar, 1957-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Gitelman, Belle S., 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Gladstone, Gerald, 1960, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Glaser, Louis, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Goldberg, Dorothy, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Goldin, Leon, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Goldstein, Howard, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Gonzalez, Xavier, 1953-1965, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
  - Goodspeed, Albert, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Goodyear, John, 1961-1968, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Gorky, Arshile, Exhibition Materials, 1969-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Gorky, Arshile, Exhibition Materials, 1980-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Gorky, Arshile, Photographs of Artwork and Catalogue Raisonné Projects, 1969-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Gorky, Arshile, Catalogue Raisonné Project, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Grillo, John, circa 1960-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Grillo, John, Printed Material, Photographs, 1955-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Haacke, Hans, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Haass, Terry, 1957-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Haese, Gunter, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hague, Raoul, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Hammersley, Frederick, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Hartung, Hans, 1957-1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Hartung, Hans and Adja Yunkers, 1958, undated; Archival Resource Key; (limited edition prints) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Hazelet, Sally, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Hepworth, Barbara, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Heron, Patrick, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Hess, Minda, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Hilton, Roger, 1959-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Hios, Theo, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Horiuchi, Paul, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Horvath, Joseph, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Hostetler, David, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Howard, Charles, 1956-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Hulich, Josef, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Istrati, Alexandre, 1957-1965, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Jacobsen, Robert, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Jaeisch, Hans, 1956-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Johnson, James, 1957-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Jones, John Paul, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Kadish, Rueben, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Kaish, Morton, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Kane, Robert, 1958-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Karoly, Fredric, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Kaufman, Irving, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Kepes, Gyorgy, 1958-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Kepes, Juliet, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - King, William, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Koenig, John F., 1958-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Kohn, Edmond, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Krasner, Lee, 1955-1964, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 47-49)
  - Krushenick, Nicholas, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Lamantina, James R., Jr., undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Lamouroux, Jean, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Legare, Juliette, 1957-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Leighton, Clare, 1957-1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Lekakis, Michael, 1959-1965, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Levee, John, 1957-1960, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Levi, Josef, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Libal, Edward, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques, 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Lister, Jeanne, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Little, John, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Long, Hubert, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - MacGibney, Bruce R., undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Maddox, Jerrold, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Maisterra, N. Jose, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Malicoat, Philip C., 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Malina, Frank, 1965-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Manessier, Alfred, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Marsciano, Nicholas, 1962-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Martine, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Mason, Alden C., 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Masurovsky, Gregory, 1958-1963, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Matsumoto, Hozan, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Matta, Roberto, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Matthews, Joan, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Mattox, Charles, 1965-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Mayhew, Richard C., undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - McGee, Winston, 1958-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - McManaway, David, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - McVey, William, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mefferd, Boyd, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Meneeley, Edward, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Meo, Salvatore S., 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Metzger, Hal, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Michaels, Glen, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Miguel, Cécile, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Millionzi, Victor, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Miró, Joan, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell, Madison Fred, 1957-1960, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Mitchell, Madison Fred, 1960-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Montgomery, Frank, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Moorman, Charlotte, 1979-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16-18)
  - Morelett, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Morin, Thomas, 1958-1960, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Morris, Kyle, 1957-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Morris, William, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Morrison, Ruth, 1961-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Morrow, Robert, 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Morse, Breton, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Mosca, Ivan, 1957-1960, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Moy, Seong, 1957-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Mueller, Robert, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Mullen, Albert, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Naberezny, Joh, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Nakian, Reuben, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Napoli, Giuseppi, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Nay, E. W., undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Nelson, Rolf, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Nesbitt, Lowell, 1965-1968, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35-36)
  - Nichols, E. E., 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Nikos (Kessanlis), 1958-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Noguchi, Isamu, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Oliver, F. M., 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Oppenheim, Dennis, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Ortman, George, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Ossorio, Alfonso, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Ott, Lynfield, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Otta, Francesco, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Pace, Stephen, 1954-1964, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 46-47)
  - Pack, Rose H., 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Paris, Harold, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Pavia, Philip, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Perilli, Achille, 1957-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Phillips, Blanche, 1959, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Potter, Bernice, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Powell, John M., Jr., 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Prokopoff, Stephen, 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Rabkin Leo (Lights in Orbit show), 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Raisen, Nathan, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Reeves, Paul, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Reinhardt, Ad, 1959-1963, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Renouf, Edward, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Rickey, George, 1963-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Riley, Bridget, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Rocklin, Raymond, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Rothko, Mark, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Salk, Rita Anne, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Salvatore, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Samuels, Edward G. (Lights in Orbit Show), 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Satok, Ronald, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Schanker, Louis, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Schiwetz, Bertold ("Tex"), 1957-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Schlemowitz, Abram, 1960-1965, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Schock, William, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Schreiber, Martin, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Schucker, Charles, 1962-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Schultze, Bernard, 1958-1957, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 75-77)
  - Sibley, Charles, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Sirugo, Sal, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Smith, David, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Smith, Mitchell, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Smith, William G., Jr., 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Soto, Jesus Raphael, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Soulages, Pierre, 1957-1960, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Soviak, Harry, 1958-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Stasik, Andrew, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Stewart, Macdonald (Phyllis Reed), 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Streeter, Tal, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Sugaï, Kumi, 1957-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Takaezu, Toshiko, 1958-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Takal, Peter, 1958-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Tanaka, Flavio Shiro, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Tania, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Terbois, Pierre, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Turcato, Giulio, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Turnbull, William, 1959-1960, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Tworkov, Jack, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Valentin, Marcelle, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Van Dyk, James, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Van Leyden, Ernst, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Vaughan, Keith, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Vavrushka, Frank, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Vazquez, Frank, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Vedova, Emilio, 1958-1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Von Wicht, John, 1957, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Wadowski, Alice T., 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Walker, Clay, 1957-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Warshaw, Laurence (Lights in Orbit show), 1967-1968, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Wayne, June, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Weatherspoon, Alexander, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Weber, Hugo, 1961-1968, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Weiner, Homer, 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Weinrib, David, 1960-1965, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24-25)
  - Wheeler, Harry, 1959-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Whiteside, Forbes, 1960-1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Whitman, Robert, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Wilke, Ulfert, 1953-1968, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29-30)
  - Wilson, Frank Avary, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Winter, Fritz, 1955-1958, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Wynter, Bryan, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Xceron, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Yamamoto, Taro, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Youngerman, R., 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Zaloudek, Duane, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Ziroli, Nicola V., 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Exhibition Files, 1957-1968; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 0.9 Linear feet Boxes 6-7
  Exhibition files for shows presented at the Howard Wise Gallery of Present Day Painting and Sculpture, Cleveland, and the Howard Wise Gallery, New York, contain correspondence, printed material and guest lists. The series is not a comprehensive record of exhibitions at the galleries, however; notably, no documentation is found of the New York gallery's opening show.
  Files are arranged chronologically.
  - Six from Paris (Cleveland opening show, Dec. 7, 1957-Jan. 18, 1958; Corneille, Barre, Bertrand, Levee, Gillet), 1958-1959, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Space - Light - Color (Cleveland, Jan. 19-March 9, 1958; Dorazio, Mitchell, Istrati), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Nature Forms in Art (Cleveland, March 9-April 20, 1958; Edwards, Peck, Mosca); Graphic Works of Hartung and Other Artists of the New School of Paris (Cleveland, March 30-[April ?], 1958; Atlan, Bissiere, Bryen, Esteve, Friedlaender, Hayter, Poliakoff, Singer, Springer), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 41-42)
  - Willi Baumeister and Five Contemporary German Painters (Cleveland, April 20-May 1958; Cavael, Jaenisch, Nay, Trier, Winter), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Bizyuta BunkBa Kyokai Art Association, Japan (Cleveland, May 28-June 29, 1958), 1957-1958, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Six Young Painters of the Howard Wise Gallery (Cleveland, June 30-July 1958; Bertschmann, Kane, Kessanlis, Quinn, Reeves, Soviak), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - An Exhibition of Paintings by Xavier Gonzalez (Cleveland, Sept. 21-Oct. 19, 1958), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - An Exhibition of Oils by 8 Painters of the Galerie Arnaud, Paris (Cleveland, Oct. 19-Nov. 18, 1958; Garrode, Dowling, Feito, Fichet, Gautier, Guitet, Koenig, Tanaka), 1957-1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Survey of Contemporary English Painting (Cleveland, Nov. 23-Dec. 27, 1958; Blow, Gear, Feiler, Frost, Hitchens, Vaughan, Wilson, Wynter), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - 18 Painters of the 1958 Pittsburgh International (Cleveland, Dec. 28, 1958-Jan. 30, 1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Fred Mitchell (Cleveland, Feb. 1-28, 1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Selections from the 1958-59 Whitney Annual (Cleveland, March 1-22, 1959), 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Adja Yunkers (Cleveland March 22-April 19, 1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Loan Exhibition, Art To-Day Around the World (Cleveland at Intown Club, April 1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Recent Accessions (Cleveland, April 19-May 17, 1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Gabor Peterdi (Cleveland, May 20-June 26, 1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Group Show (Cleveland, Sept. 1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Georgy Kepes (Cleveland, Sept. 20-Oct. 17, 1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Group Show (Cleveland, Oct. 4-29, 1959; Briggs, Dugmore, Grillo, Krasner, McNeil, Mitchell, Pace, Resnick), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Teenage Paintings from Israel (Cleveland, Oct. 18-25, 1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Ethel Edwards (Cleveland, Oct. 25-Nov. 21, 1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - James Johnson (Cleveland, Nov. 22-Dec. 19, 1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - 6 of Paris (Cleveland, Dec, 20, 1959-Jan. 9, 1960; Sugaï, Levee, Barré, Gillet, Corneille), 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Recent Paintings by Milton Resnick (Cleveland, Jan. 10-Feb. 29, 1960), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Four Contemporary English Painters (Cleveland, Feb. 14-March 12, 1960; Bell, Frost, Hilton, Turnbull), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Present Day Paris Painting (Cleveland, March 13-April 9, 1960; Bertrand, Francken, Corneille, Levee, Istrati, Koenig, Dumitresco), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Stephen Pace (New York, March 29-April 23; Cleveland, April 10-May 7, 1960), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Near-Cleveland Invitational Exhibition (Cleveland, May 8-June 4, 1960), 1958-1960, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Some Painters from Tenth Street (Cleveland, June 6-July 12, 1960), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - The Works of Edward Dugmore (Cleveland, Sept 8-Oct. 1, 1960), 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Loan Exhibition (Cleveland at Women's City Club, circa Oct. 1-circa Dec. 15, 1960), 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Elaine de Kooning (Cleveland, Oct. 31-26, 1960), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Augustus Peck (Cleveland, Nov. 29-Dec. 24, 1960), 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Harry Bertschmann (Cleveland, Dec. 27, 1980-Jan. 21, 1961), 1957-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Drawings by Auguste Rodin, Watercolors by George McNeil, and Prints by Stanley William Hayter (Cleveland, Jan. 23-Feb. 18, 1961), 1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - A Selection of Paintings and Watercolors by Piero Dorazio (Cleveland, Feb. 20-March 18, 1961), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Movement in Art (Cleveland, March 20-April 15, 1961; Agam, Corneille, Lye, Tinguely), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Recent Paintings by James Johnson (Cleveland, April 17-May 13, 1961), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Works of Art Acquired by Cleveland Collectors Through the Howard Wise Gallery (Cleveland, May 15-June 10, 1961), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Recent Paintings by Fred Mitchell (Cleveland, June 12-July 8, 1961), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - George McNeil and Stephen Pace (traveling exhibition), 1961-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 80-87)
    Scope and Contents
    Missing Title
    General Correspondence, 1961-1962
    Refusals, 1961-1962
    Transportation, 1961-1962
    Rose Art Museum, Brandeis University, 1961
    Walker Art Center, 1961-1962
    Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1961-1962
    Arts Club of Chicago, 1961-1962
    Kalamazoo Art Center, 1961-1962
  - On the Move, Kinetic Sculpture (New York, Jan. 9-Feb.1, 1964), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Recent Paintings by Milton Resnick (New York, Feb. 4-29, 1964), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - The Ten U.S.A. Sculptors of the 1963 Sao Paulo Bienal (New York, March 5-28, 1964), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Vesey's Gala Garden (New York, May 27-June 19, 1964), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Debut: First New York Showing of Three Young American Artists (New York, Sept. 29-Oct. 17, 1964; Celentano, Komodore, Raisen), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Paintings by George McNeil (New York, Oct. 20-Nov. 7, 1964), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Group Zero: Mack, Piene, Uecker (New York, Nov. 12-Dec. 5, 1964), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Stanley William Hayter - Peter Sedgley - Ulfert Wiulkie: Three One-Man Shows (New York, Jan. 12-20, 1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Oster's Magic Moirés (New York, Feb. 4-27, 1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Len Lye's Bounding Steel Sculptures (New York, March 6-April 3, 1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Computer-Generated Pictures by Bela Julesz and Michael Noll (New York, April 6-24, 1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Herbert Bayer - Charles Howard - Charmion Von Wiegand: Three One-Man Shows (New York, April 27-May 15, 1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - New Faces - New York (New York, May 18-June 18, 1965; Feitelson, Levi, Mattox, Nesbitt, Nizuma), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Lowell Nesbitt: Flowers, Facades and IBM Machines (New York, Sept. 21-Oct. 9, 1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cinecromaticos by Abraham Palatnik of Brazil; Površine by Ivan Picelj of Yugoslavia: Two One-Man Shows (New York, Oct. 12-30, 1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Otto Piene, Light Ballet (New York, Nov. 2-20, 1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Bernard Schultze (New York, Nov. 23-Dec. 11, 1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Hans Haacke, Wind and Water; Gerald Oster, Moirés and Phosphenes (New York, Jan. 4-22, 1966), 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Julio Le Parc (New York, Feb. 1-19, 1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Yvaral (New York, Feb. 23-March 12, 1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Bill Komodore (New York, March 15-April 2, 1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Heinz Mack, Lights of Silver (New York, April 5-30, 1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Paintings by Francis Celentano; Sculptures in Stone by Minoru Nizuma (New York, May 3-28, 1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Bruno Munari (New York, Sept. 20-Oct. 8, 1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)